TYPHOON FAMILY
Yes, sir.
NINE YEARS AGO
I'm sorry to bother you again,
but I'd like to ask for another favor.
As you know,
come tomorrow, I'll go bankrupt.
I'll give you some shares.
No, it's not worthless!
How is that worthless?
Don't you trust me? I'm Pyo--
Hello?
KOREA TELECOM
TYPHOON TRADING
"Promissory note."
In… return for borrowing
PROMISSORY NOTE
forty million won…
CREDITOR: KANG JIN-YOUNG
DEBTOR: PYO BAK-HO
Mr. Kang…
"Promissory note"?
I can't recall if such a thing existed.
The money from nine years ago
should now be…
What with the interest… No.
Throw in all the overdue interest,
and this office
and the building should be mine.
Watch your darn mouth, you little brat.
Don't you worry.
I couldn't care less about your building.
Then what?
I want the three million pairs
of gloves in your storage.
What?
I'm losing out big time, aren't I?
What's the matter?
Do you think I don't have it?
That may be the case.
Let me share the order of events.
Once Typhoon Trading delivers the gloves
and the payment has been received,
our transaction will be complete.
That promissory note or whatever
will be given to you.
Why should I make this deal with you?
It's obvious.
You have much more to lose.
But I can't
just give you the stuff
solely based on your words.
Let's do this.
LETTER OF GUARANTEE
The terms are the same.
But on the day the payment is made,
you will hand over
the promissory note to me.
What if you fail to do so?
What can you offer?
You have no money, so not that.
Typhoon Trading.
I don't know.
My company?
That's not something
I can offer as I please.
Let's think realistically.
I offer myself.
To be exact, my position.
You'll give up everything
and leave the business alone?
The position of CEO
at Typhoon Trading, you say?
Is it a balanced deal now?
You better have it
if you want to save that petty position
your father left behind.
3. IF THE PROMISSORY NOTE IS NOT RETURNED,
KANG TAE-POONG SHALL RESIGN
FROM TYPHOON TRADING
1. PYO MERCHANT MARINE TO TRANSFER
3 MILLION GLOVES
2. TYPHOON TRADING TO RETURN
THE PROMISSORY NOTE
You can't come crying to me later.
JUNE 5TH, 1998
HOWEVER, OTHER EMPLOYEES
OF TYPHOON TRADING
SHALL NOT BE IMPACTED IN ANY WAY
THROUGH THE CONTENTS OF THIS CONTRACT
KANG TAE-POONG
PYO BAK-HO
Oh, it almost slipped my mind.
Don't you want to know
why I need those gloves?
Because someone set
our warehouse on fire.
But I never beg.
I make others beg.
I'm getting a call.
Hello?
Hey, Ms. Oh. What's up?
What?
We got the gloves, so we can deliver them
straight to the designated warehouse.
Mr. Bae just went out
to look for a truck himself.
Yes, you can do that.
Okay, bye.
MOMO'S PUB
I don't know about everyone else,
but I thought I should apologize to you.
Pick up the pace,
and we can all wrap up quickly.
Speed it up even more,
and we'll be out in no time.
Hey, watch your step.
Don't you dare touch them!
You bastards.
So, did you come
looking for a fight, Tae-poong?
Bring it on. Come at me, you punk.
Jerk.
Ms. Oh.
Are you out of your mind?
You did it, didn't you?
-What?
-I know everything.
You set the place on fire.
I don't know what you mean.
So shut your mouth and wait.
Let's go.
Give me that!
PURCHASE AGREEMENT
"Seller, Pyo Bak-ho"?
Darn it!
Ms. Oh.
Can we…
Can we stay like this for a moment?
I really want
to say something to comfort you,
but I don't know what to say.
Ms. Cha came by.
Did she tell you everything?
I was going to take my time
and tell you later.
What about your hand?
He has thick skin,
so it must've hurt a lot.
So here's what happened.
-First, I said I had the promissory note.
-Take your time.
You can take your time to tell me.
My hand isn't the problem right now.
It's how you're feeling.
Are you all right?
I'm…
Well…
I'm okay, I guess.
I just feel bad for my father.
It would've broken his heart
if he had seen all this.
He would've said you've done well.
EPISODE 14
BORN IN THE WIND
TYPHOON TRADING
Yes.
Yes, thank you.
-So?
-Yeah.
The insurance company handled everything.
So is the case closed as arson?
Well, it was an arson case.
But there's insufficient evidence,
so it'll remain unresolved.
I'm just glad the insurance can cover it.
We just got over another hurdle.
Will it take about a month
for the payment?
Yes, I've issued the invoice,
so the payment will be made in a month.
Good. We finally caught a breather
thanks to Mr. Kang.
All right. Good work, everyone.
After all, it's summer vacation season.
Why don't we use this chance
to get some fresh air?
-I'm sure you're all feeling down.
-Well, we'll get over this.
Who would feel great after this?
What's wrong with Seon-taek, really?
She isn't someone who'd do that,
so she must've lost her senses.
I was greatly disappointed too.
Ms. Cha?
Have you lost your mind?
How dare you show up here?
I'll leave these and go.
I was designated to this area.
Then you should change it.
Swap your area with someone else.
I'm all done here and leaving. Okay?
Cha Seon-taek!
You are less than human
and worse than the beasts.
How dare you brazenly show up here?
Then what can I do?
You can stop ordering
after this month's subscription.
I guess you haven't heard.
ACCOUNT BOOK
I already lodged a complaint
with your juice company
for the damage you caused
to our official documents.
Your company had a solid reputation,
so why would they keep you?
-Myung-gwan.
-And Mr. Kang.
I also sued her for trespassing and theft,
so that's all you need to know.
Mr. Koo.
How can you be so cruel?
What did I do so wrong?
Think of all the years
we've known each other!
The years?
What did that mean to you?
When you sold away 26 years
for a petty amount of money,
did this mean anything to you?!
Think of how desperate I was.
I can't believe not a single person here
asked me why I did it.
If you were going through something
that made you do this,
you should've told us about it!
If I were
to tell you all about my business,
it'd be like speaking ill of my family!
But are we strangers?
Are we?
We said we'd be your family!
We already know
you have no one else to rely on.
All of us here are all living
in such misery anyway!
So why did you feel ashamed
and want to hide this,
only to end up in this state?
Why should the miserable stick together?
We have to take something from the rich!
You're hopeless. Get out of here!
Don't ever show your face here again!
I'm going to starve to death anyway.
We don't have to meet again!
Can you please stop?
-This is too frightening and upsetting.
-Ms. Cha, that's enough for today.
You should leave for now.
Why…
won't you apologize?
Say you're sorry.
Say you were wrong.
And I don't mean to me,
but to your colleagues and my father.
You need to apologize to them.
My dear.
Will an apology change anything?
-Please just beg for forgiveness.
-So what if I beg?
Are you going to forgive me?
If I apologize,
can the late Mr. Kang hear anything I say?
Yes.
He'll hear you.
He may be dead, but he's not gone.
No, right?
All of us here remember him.
I'll hear it. We'll hear it.
My father will hear it too.
And you'll hear it too.
I can't understand
or forgive you for this.
But still,
you should understand…
and forgive yourself for this.
Living with guilt toward my father?
I'm already carrying enough
of that myself.
If that is the case,
if he's listening,
that's all the more reason I can't say it.
I can't do it.
A whale breathes through the blowhole
on top of its head.
-Mi-seon, isn't that nice?
-It is.
But you never did anything like that.
Why are you using cosmetic products?
It's as if you're dating someone.
I am dating someone.
Wait, what? Who is it?
Is it Tae-poong?
Oh, my goodness.
What do you see in him?
Wait, does he like you?
My gosh. This is insane.
He's an unusual one too.
You didn't lend him money
or something like that, did you?
Don't be cheeky.
-By any chance, have you two kissed?
-Stop saying that in front of a kid.
It's time to sleep, Beom. It's late.
-Mi-seon.
-Yes?
Is the sea that big?
Yes, the sea
is much bigger than Han River.
-It's blue and vast.
-I don't think so.
It's not so big.
So how do blue whales live there,
and how does it have treasures?
You fool.
It's because you're watching it
on a tiny TV.
It's really huge in real life.
I'm not a fool, you old hag.
What did you say?
I'm the only one
who hasn't seen the sea. Gosh.
Get over here.
Get over here! Did you call me a hag?
I'm going to tickle you!
Tickles, doesn't it?
Doesn't it? That's what you get
for calling me a hag!
Get back here!
Did you want to see the sea
that badly, my dear Beom?
FOR LEASE
ULCHI WORLD REAL ESTATE OFFICE
I just paged Mi-seon,
so she'll be here soon.
Promissory note.
Where would the promissory note be?
Oh, my.
Gosh, why is it so dusty?
Hold on.
Mi-seon?
It's just that
I can't see anything right now.
Jeez.
CHEONGGYE POLICE STATION
Excuse me, I received a call to come here.
-Are you his guardian?
-Yes.
He was reported
for trespassing and vandalism.
Okay.
Mr. Kang?
Gosh.
You need to dust yourself off a little.
You're going to break Ms. Jung's heart.
Gosh, I'm so hungry.
-I'm hungry.
-Are you?
Yes.
Jeez.
What?
Well, you know.
-We were on the same page.
-We were.
-You can have this later.
-Okay. Thanks.
Here. You love this. Have some.
Mr. Kang.
"Mr. Kang"?
Man, "Mr. Kang"?
You're on a break.
I really don't want to be called that.
-I'm your boyfriend.
-Okay.
Mr. Kang Tae-poong.
Exactly. We're on a break.
What are we doing here?
I have to find it quickly.
I was feeling rushed
and I'm running out of time.
-If I don't, the business will--
-One second.
Clear your mind for one second.
Have you been sleeping
or eating since that day?
What you need
is a moment to relax your mind.
You're right.
-It's good.
-Is it?
I prepared something for you.
Here.
Open it.
G2 DIGITAL PCS
STAY CONNECTED ANYWHERE
It's a real cell phone.
Is this for me?
This is mine!
What was that?
Were you just showing it off?
Look.
Number one on my speed dial.
"Oh Mi-seon" with a heart.
-What?
-Why won't it connect?
Why isn't this working?
What do you mean?
Jeez, I barely have any reception!
Why won't it work?
-Come on.
-What is it?
-I've found a signal.
-What's that sound?
Look.
This is yours.
We should've bought this ages ago.
We're the only two salespeople
who don't have cell phones.
Is this really for me?
You didn't have to get one for me.
Thank you.
-Do you like it?
-This is so light.
I think it's as heavy as a block of tofu.
-What kind of an analogy is that?
-No?
So, what now?
Will I be number one on your speed dial?
-Yes.
-What will you save my name as?
Your name, Kang Tae-poong.
You'd be on top. It's the first letter
of the Korean alphabet.
You can be so dry.
Just Kang Tae-poong? How about…
You can go with Honey-poong
or Baby-poong, something like that.
-Honey-poong?
-Yes.
Honey-poong? Okay.
But that'll put you last on the list.
Is that okay?
No, I want to be number one.
I mean that you'd be at the bottom
in the actual contacts.
Then just use the first alphabet.
-The first?
-Or Baby-poong.
I knew it. We have such good chemistry.
Is the sea a sky for whales?
I'm sorry for making you worried today.
"Anyway."
"What is on your
mind?"
"Are you thinking about me…"
Where's the question mark?
The question mark.
My gosh!
One more time.
"What are you up to?"
You're finally home after days,
so why are you texting
instead of sleeping?
Mom.
Do you want me to check your biorhythm?
I can check it here.
-Is it accurate?
-Of course.
Your date of birth.
Why don't we take a day trip
to the sea with Beom?
And then, let's go look
for the promissory note.
Sounds great!
My condition is great? How so?
Everything about you is great.
Everything, including your skin.
I've always had good skin.
That's untrustworthy.
"I would…
love to."
ALL VEHICLES MUST CHECK IN
AT THE SECURITY OFFICE
Did you get this from that woman?
Yes, I received it
from Ms. Cha Seon-taek herself today.
I thought she got fired
from the juice company.
-She must've had someone to borrow from.
-She sold her house.
Of course.
She shouldn't have slept in peace
before she paid my money back.
What's your plan now?
Tae-poong, that kid,
knows about the promissory note,
but he doesn't have it.
He had no idea money wasn't the problem,
but our shares were at stake.
"Pyo Bak-ho will
transfer 20% of his shares…"
No.
"Transfer 30% of his shares…"
What about the flight?
I'll send him away as soon as possible.
Have him stay abroad
and study for about three years.
By then, Kang Tae-poong
would've been gone without a trace.
CEO OFFICE
Dad!
-Send my driver home. You may leave too.
-Yes, sir.
What were you two talking about?
PURCHASE AGREEMENT
Dad. No.
Mr. Pyo.
I went through such a ridiculous incident.
And my family was behind it.
-Why did you set the place on fire?
-That's not the problem!
Why did you sell my gloves to that idiot?
Yes, I set the place on fire.
I knew it was dangerous,
but I put up with the risk
and did that. Do you know why?
Because I wanted you…
to be proud of me just once.
And you chose to set the place on fire?
You idiot!
Have you considered
the kind of consequences you'd face?
That's the very proof of your idiocy!
I'm dumb, and you're so smart
that you had to borrow money
from Typhoon Trading?
What's wrong?
Did you think I didn't know a thing?
Tae-poong always gets the best of you…
because you let him
get a hold of your weakness!
You wicked punk. Do you know
how I kept this business going?
I should've had a son like Tae-poong,
not an idiot like you!
Dad…
-You can't say that to me.
-Why not?
My business wouldn't be in this state
if a smart kid like him were my son!
You can't do a thing without me!
But Tae-poong is out there
spreading his wings without his dad!
All you ever do is pull tricks
and look for excuses!
You're a loser.
Get out.
Go and get ready to go to America.
I don't want to see you here. Get out!
Why do you call me a loser?
PYO BAK-HO
Dad.
I'm not a loser.
I'm not a loser!
Tae-poong is the thief.
He keeps stealing everything that's mine.
The girls,
the fabric, the shoes, the gloves,
and…
even you, Dad.
He even took you from me.
Gosh.
Dad.
I once heard somewhere
that people don't die that easily.
So,
wait here just a little, okay?
I'll get my victory
against that punk, Tae-poong,
and come back to get you.
So…
hang in there for a while.
Light you up at the end of the night
As you flowed in your loneliness
You did not enjoy any of your days
And crossed winter with a blank face
Wang Nam-mo.
Make me something to eat.
Why haven't you eaten yet?
Mind your own business.
Then, why are you strumming alone
instead of meeting gumiho?
Mom.
Have you ever heard me sing?
Of course, I have.
When you were in third grade,
you were chosen to sing
the national anthem on the field day.
But not since then.
What do you say?
Should I sing something now?
No, don't bother me while I eat.
Just listen to it. It's not so bad.
-Forget it.
-Okay.
Her smile
Is like a full-bloomed magnolia
You have a pretty nice voice.
And you're good with the guitar.
Whenever I looked at her
It was always like a warm spring day
On the day she first cried
I was shocked out of my mind
Her beautiful face
Was covered with tears
She always smiled no matter the pain
But on the day she first shed tears
KIM EUL-NYEO
DEPUTY BRANCH MANAGER
It felt like the world came crashing down
There, there.
I felt so stifled on the inside
But I can't see it anymore
The way she smiled
On the day she first cried
She left my life
Why on earth…
do kids grow up this fast?
It feels like
I didn't even get to see you much.
What have I lived for all these years?
Mom.
Ms. Eul-nyeo.
I love you.
You're driving me crazy.
Come on out, Mi-ho!
Oh, my.
Why did you get two watermelons?
Those must've been heavy!
They were so light
I thought they were tangerines.
Show me your hands.
With all this stuff,
your hands must've been sore.
Hey, Nam-mo.
This is for you and Grandma.
Gosh, you didn't have to get us one.
Little Ms. Oh, you should be
fully dressed before you walk out.
I'm fully dressed.
Oh, my. You're unbelievable.
You can't go around looking like this,
exposing all of your body!
My goodness. I can't believe it.
I don't want to wear this, Ms. Jung!
-You have to!
-This is fashion!
You can't go out like this.
People will be
terrified of you in this state.
-No, she's just my style.
-Silence.
You look much better.
Good grief, Ms. Jung.
Here comes the peacock.
He's just born that good-looking.
Looking racy and nice. Good.
Where's Mi-seon?
Let's go! I'm ready.
Why do you have so much stuff?
I boiled some eggs and corn and packed
side dishes, lettuce, and chili peppers.
These will cost money outside.
Please stop acting so miserably stingy.
Why? I love how smart she is.
-Well, please keep an eye on my grandma.
-You love it?
She's been sleeping a lot lately.
Cut it out.
The elderly tend to lose energy
in the dead of summer.
Have a relaxing time there.
Thank you. We'll make it quick.
Nice job with the brows.
-So what?
-"So what?"
-Back at you.
-No, you.
-You're so annoying!
-Hey, Beom!
We'll leave if you don't come out!
-Oh, my.
-Wow.
-Look at you.
-I'm nothing compared to that guy.
He's the real deal.
The sea is calling out to me!
SAMPO, THE BEACH OF LOVE AND ROMANCE
Tubes for rent!
Oh, wow.
-Mi-seon, how far does the sea stretch?
-Everything you see out there is the sea.
Are you scared? Come here.
Come to me.
Let's go and look at the sea!
Here we go.
Beom, the sea is vast and deep.
The sea stretches all the way to there.
-Then we'll die if we go that far.
-Is that so?
What do you think is under the sea?
-Hey.
-That's cold.
It feels cool.
There are waves,
sand, and fish in the sea.
And whales and treasures.
That's right.
Even when you face
something big and scary,
try to think of what's inside.
No matter how vast the sea is,
in the end,
it all began with this cool water.
-Hey!
-What?
Hey, Beom, with this, you won't die
even if you go all the way out there.
-Put it on.
-Put it on!
Hey, the sun's going down.
Let's have fun already!
-Be careful! Don't fall!
-Let's go!
-Oh, my!
-It's so cold!
Come on in!
Come and join us!
Did you just splash me?
Get back here! Back here!
Come join us!
There.
So muscular.
Catch me if you can!
I said catch me, not toss me in the water!
-I'm sorry.
-What am I going to do?
I'm leaving!
Wang Nam-mo!
Wang Nam-mo, you! I'm going to kill you!
Stay here, Beom.
Mr. Kang Tae-poong.
You were thinking about work again.
I was thinking about my girlfriend.
This won't do. Come here.
-Why?
-Come.
-Do we leave him there?
-Yes, just for a moment.
Mr. Kang, look over here.
There are clams everywhere! Look.
Do you see these seaweeds in here?
The clams are the ones eating it.
It's this clam. Littleneck clam.
This is what you're looking for.
Littleneck clams.
Wait.
What? What is it?
Is this sea mustard?
I found some sea mustard.
Why was it there?
Look at this.
It's sea mustard, right?
Yes, it is, and there's a bunch of them.
So look for littleneck clams
instead of that.
So sea mustard isn't actually a plant.
If you think about it,
it shouldn't be called seaweed.
It's marine algae.
Marine algae.
Stop looking for marine algae.
You can look for these now.
The seaweed soup we had together
last birthday was so delicious.
My goodness! Let's go eat.
Let's go.
Let's just go home.
We can go home for food.
I have plenty of it.
I'm actually out of side dishes.
Happy birthday to our new employee,
-Kang Tae-poong!
-Cheers.
Cheers.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Thank you.
-Happy birthday.
-Thank you.
-You should eat.
It's delicious.
It's good.
We can't collect these after sunset.
So hurry up and find some.
Find some more. Yes, that's it.
You're taking the marine algae home?
More sea mustard.
This feels like manual labor.
Anyway.
How did Littleneck 1 and Littleneck 2
end up getting caught by us?
-Stop naming them. We'll be eating them.
-What?
I gathered those as food.
-There's a huge clam.
-Where?
Where is it?
Oops, I tripped!
Gosh.
Hey, be careful.
Hey, my littleneck clams.
Why did you do that?
Well, after spending
a few hours with them, they grew on me.
They grew on you that quickly?
How can I eat those cute things?
-My gosh.
-Oh, dear.
But you had nothing else on your mind
while doing this, right?
That's so true.
I had nothing else on my mind.
Neither the promissory note
nor Pyo Merchant Marine.
That's good enough then. That will do.
Oh, right! Try to guess what I brought.
Did you bring something?
-Look.
-What is that?
It's a top shell. It hangs onto sounds,
so you can hear waves in it.
Let me hear it.
-You can, right? Can you?
-You're right. I can.
-My gosh. Yes.
-You hear it, right?
I can.
I love you.
Can you hear my feelings?
I can hear it loud and clear.
You got something on your face.
I think your hand is dirtier.
-No.
-Are you putting it on my face?
No way. Look.
You're getting more on me.
No way.
Then Ji-yeong,
who ranked second in her class,
pushed Min-ji,
the top student, off the rooftop.
Why?
And Min-ji fell headfirst.
After that incident,
Ji-yeong was at her evening study session.
Soon, she realized
she was there all alone.
-Then she began to hear something.
-Okay.
Thump, thump, thump.
"She's not here."
"She's not here either."
Thump, thump, thump.
Thump.
"She's here!"
She's here!
-Stop it!
-Don't do that!
-She's here!
-Stop it!
-That was so shocking!
-Mi-seon's good at this.
-Hey, forget it.
-Why are you so shocked?
Why was she there?
I feel bad for that girl, though.
-Ranking second is still good.
-Right?
Hey, Beom. Forget that.
Have a bite, go inside and go to sleep.
I'm not sleepy.
Stop telling me to go to sleep.
Beom, do you want your brother-in-law
to sing you a lullaby?
I decline, Mr. Wang Nam-mo.
Are you leaving? Good night.
That was so shocking.
My gosh.
Ji-yeong sounds so evil. How awful.
-How can she push her?
-Hello.
Hello? Can I speak to Mi-ho?
Who would call at this hour?
No one.
-Who was it?
-Someone had the wrong number.
It was the wrong number. A stranger.
-I mean it.
-You're acting odd.
-I'm serious.
-Is she cheating on you?
I said no.
-But she's acting suspicious.
-It's no one.
She can't cheat.
What do you mean, I can't?
What's with you, Mi-seon?
Hey, why is your ex-boyfriend
looking for you?
You mean Tae-min?
-Why didn't you put me on?
-Hey!
Why do you stay in touch
with your ex-boyfriend?
Because I had to say something to him.
Anyway, if he calls again, put me on.
Hey!
You're not up to anything, are you?
I'm not. What's with you?
She seems so suspicious.
-Are you sure you can sleep here?
-I'll be fine.
I like sleeping in the car.
The tent is too small,
so let Nam-mo and Beom stay.
And you can relax with Mi-ho.
It seems uncomfortable.
It feels so nice and comfy.
Go to sleep.
It doesn't seem all right.
Gosh.
It's so relaxing.
You're really going to go to sleep?
I'm tired.
And we have to get up early tomorrow.
Can we talk?
Later. Let's talk later.
Later. You always say later.
You said you'll take up another job
after this summer break.
Even now, I only see you
in the dead of night. How is this dating?
It's just a late-night stroll.
Why? I like seeing you like this
even if it's for a brief moment.
Do you not feel that way?
No, I don't.
Darn it. Forget it. Whatever.
It could be somewhere here.
The ceiling…
What's this?
Let's see.
It looks old.
Could it be…
Why is this here?
1986 STUDENT RECORD
ETHICS B, KOREAN D, MATH F, SCIENCE F,
PHYSICAL EDUCATION A, ENGLISH D
HE MAY HAVE AWFUL GRADES,
BUT HE HAS AN EXEMPLARY PERSONALITY
It's been so long.
I APOLOGIZE FOR MY SON'S POOR PERFORMANCE
PLEASE CONTINUE TO GUIDE HIM WELL
That's so dad.
"I apologize
for my son's poor performance."
My gosh.
You must've been surprised
when my sister hung up.
Sorry.
Anyway, have you considered
what I said last time?
Don't be like this, Tae-min.
You said you'd love to.
You're just awful.
Don't be so awful.
I'd like to do that one of these days.
It's not like that.
Hey!
Good luck with him.
Hey, Nam-mo!
Darn it.
What's going on?
What are you looking for?
The promissory note?
Well, I heard
this car was his favorite thing.
I thought it might be here somewhere.
What happens if you don't find it?
The deadline is coming up.
In that case…
I have to give up
my position as the CEO.
-What did you say? Ouch!
-Wait.
-Are you okay? What happened?
-Wait. Darn it.
Are you okay? Is the car okay?
Are you okay, Mi-seon?
Give up what? Your position as the CEO?
What are you talking about?
Well, I couldn't sit around
and let the business go bankrupt.
And from the company's perspective,
me leaving is the easiest way
to handle things.
How is that easy?
Jeez!
That must hurt.
So what are you…
After all that,
you're talking about moving offices?
It was a promise.
-Six!
-Hey.
-Okay.
-What now?
-All of a sudden?
-Okay.
He's so mean.
Zero.
Three.
I am back.
You're back, Mr. Bae!
Everything went well thanks to you!
So while we're on the subject,
why don't I get promoted
to manager when this deal ends?
Manager Bae.
Was he a part of the company?
-Is he on the payroll?
-Not really.
-Good work.
So?
What do you want to do once we get paid?
How about some barbecue
at Jangsu Barbecue Restaurant?
Let's eat some ribeye.
True love can be expressed
when cash is exchanged, you know.
I'll leave you at that. You know, right?
I want us to return to our old office.
I miss my old desk.
I miss that place.
I made my promise on that day.
That we'd go back to our old office
the first thing when we made money.
What if we don't find it?
Do you have a plan for that?
I'll face it when the moment comes.
Good grief.
Stop that.
Don't do it.
What's that? Is that a piece of paper?
-Is that it?
-No, not this one.
Why not? Let me see it.
-It's nothing.
-That might be it.
Should we look for it tomorrow?
Gosh.
-Mi-seon.
-Yes?
Mi-ho is laying down,
but she keeps swearing.
-What? She did?
-Go and scold her.
All right. Go to sleep.
Will you sleep here?
Why would she swear?
TYPHOON TRADING
Please put it there for now.
Okay.
Why won't he pick up?
Mr. Kang.
You're going to visit Mr. Pyo?
He's not picking up.
He's not, but today is the day
we agreed on, so I have to show up.
I'll go with you.
Listen.
I'll take this too.
What's that?
A cashier's check.
The price for the gloves
you took from him.
No, we got those gloves
in return for the money he owed us.
I know. The amount he borrowed in 1989
along with the interest
is much more than the gloves we took.
But it's also true
that you didn't find the promissory note.
There's a letter of guarantee.
And that letter is the acknowledgement
that there is a promissory note out there.
So I'll meet him today
and make an offer to just call it even.
Okay, let's hurry.
I'm not here to fight today.
I have an appointment.
Mr. Pyo is busy.
-Call him before you come!
-He won't pick up! What can I do?
I have to meet him today!
But is he inside?
What now? Are you doubting me?
Doubting, my foot.
-Move aside!
-Hey, wait!
-Hey!
-Security!
Why do you keep avoiding me?
What?
Where's Mr. Pyo?
What's he talking about?
Introducing himself?
Where's the CEO?
CEO PYO BAK-HO
Hey. Where's your dad?
You little punk.
Why do you keep asking for him?
-Say it to me if you need to talk.
-I have nothing to say to you.
Where's the CEO?
I'm the CEO.
Cut this crap and tell me.
Goodness, I'm sorry.
Why, you…
How dare you barge in here? Get out.
Stop lurking around and get out!
Okay, I'll go.
The CEO isn't even around.
This looks adequate.
-What's the time, Ms. Oh?
-It's 11:15 a.m.
What the heck are you doing?
All of you saw me here.
I came here on the scheduled date.
Let's go.
KANG TAE-POONG
11:15 A.M., JUNE 29TH, 1998
That's a permanent marker.
Did you notice the desk?
He really seemed absent.
I noticed.
What do you think happened to him?
We'll see in time.
Let's go. It's a good day,
and everyone's waiting.
Okay.
This place brings back so many emotions.
Be quiet and get me water.
Sure, it's placed inside the pantry.
Do we have to make such a huge fuss?
-Where are the scissors?
-They're on my desk.
You're making this worse.
Can you play just one song?
Is this broken?
Mr. Kang, I get it,
but you're wearing white pants
with your shirt buttoned down there.
Isn't that too revealing?
I know a thing or two about fashion.
Watch out, Myung-gwan.
We've returned in glory!
No!
Are you okay?
-Come on!
-What's this?
What is this?
You should've set this out
after the plant came in!
Come on!
Let us cut the tape
to celebrate Typhoon Trading's return.
I will call out Typhoon Trading.
Then, everyone, please shout out,
"We can do it!"
Typhoon Trading!
We can do it!
You didn't set a timer?
I didn't set a timer.
Me neither.
What did we just do? Are you guys dumb?
Mr. Bae, you should've set up the timer.
Hey, why are you getting on my case?
That's not my vibe today.
Hey, that's not my vibe today either.
Then should I do it? Or Myung-gwan?
His hands keep trembling.
Let's just take turns.
-Let's put these back together.
-Let's do it.
Should I bring the stapler?
It's too ragged.
-Right. A stapler.
-I'll bring it anyway.
-What are we doing?
-We can just stick them back together.
Is that right? Okay. All set.
-We're set.
-Okay.
Did you stick them together?
Hey, you'll staple your hand!
-I won't. Be careful.
-No!
Come on!
Typhoon Trading!
We can do it!
One, two, three.
Anyway.
Where did Pyo Bak-ho go?
Forget about him on a good day like this.
He's not around. What can he do?
Why won't you use the CEO's office?
I want to leave the place as is.
I also like it out here.
This rice cake is nice and chewy,
just like our future.
-I can't seem to swallow it.
-It's choking me.
Anyway, where's Mr. Bae?
He went out to pick up a call.
What? He's been on the phone
for half a day now.
-He's back.
-Mr. Bae.
Have some rice cake, Mr. Bae.
Have some.
Mr. Bae.
-Is something going on?
-Hey, what's wrong?
Mr. Bae.
What's wrong?
Mr. Bae, what's going on?
It's my dad.
He's going to kill himself.
What am I going to do?
BORN IN THE WIND
TYPHOON FAMILY
Dad… Dad!
And yet, they proceeded
to declare bankruptcy right away.
That does seem fishy,
but what I find odd
is that I ran into Hyun-jun there.
It's voice-activated.
It follows the source of the sound.
My father had it patented.
You two are walking
unusually close together.
Be careful, okay?
You could end up catching feelings.
Get the hell out!
If you got lost without a fuss,
everyone outside
could at least keep their jobs.
Wait for me, Dad.
I won't ever give up.
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn